Criss-Cross, are you available to help us?
Okay, I'll help you.
If you really want, I'll protect Jolyne.
I'm gonna take this creepy old geezer out!
Direction facing southeast, 127
degrees, 30 minutes, 20 seconds.
Just be aware you won't survive this time.
West-southwest, 225 degrees, zero minutes.
Hey, FF, he's right behind you!
I'm telling you, your real
enemy is that insane old man.
No way!
Now his arm is flying right
to the back of FF's head!
There is no freaking way
that was a coincidence.
That inmate's glasses flew straight at
FF and lodged themselves in their face?
Unfortunate direction.
I'm starting to understand.
It's feng shui in action.
It's geomancy for the East Asians.
With that dragon stand, Kenzo can perfectly
control the direction of his attack.
FF, next unlucky spot is here,
right above your left ear. Feel it?
Yes, that did just happen.
My stand attack has merged
with the course of your death.
No! FF!
This is bad. Really bad!
Don't touch them.
There's no point.
The unlucky direction
exists in our bodies, too.
That can only mean one thing.
It means that once the direction's chosen,
no organism can defend themselves or
escape the cruel inevitability of dying.
His next target will be...
you, Jolene. Hi-ya!
You misunderstood.
When I said this is bad just now, it
wasn't about the giant hole in FF's head.
To be totally honest,
the plain fact that they're injured
and bleeding is more of a relief.
Here's the bad thing.
There's barely any blood at all.
Their wounds are so severe that there's
not enough fluids left to keep them alive.
All the FFs in their body are
almost completely wiped out!
I'm so happy none of it spilled.
But still, that's unlucky for sure.
Thank
you
so
much for watching.
Come and find a way I'm
I am To the top Break out We are coming
I am I
am
I am
Don't stop beating!
I'm mad!
What?
Come back here, Dragon!
How dare you!
Son of a...
You're losing your touch,
old man! Never again.
I'll never be careless and step
away from the safe direction again.
I knew better than that,
and I am better than that.
Son of a...
He got away from me to a safe direction.
But still, speaking of directions,
I'm learning something valuable here.
How I can best breach them.
A mirror!
I need a mirror right now!
If I can create a mirror mid-air,
I can beam the dragon's
reflection off its surface
and fool Kenzo into moving
away from his safe space!
That gives me the perfect window to
beat up that rotting bag of skin!
What I need the most is water!
I can use water to make
a mirror, obviously.
I need it to recover
from my injuries, too.
But the only way I can possibly make a
mirror mid-air is if I can get some water.
In the not-so-distant past,
some 30,000 loyal disciples of mine
worshipped me, eagerly learned my teachings,
and rapidly followed in my footsteps.
But not now.
Ever since being incarcerated here,
their love and loyalty has
turned into pure disgust.
Everyone looked down on me,
laughed, and turned away.
Even degenerates that
abducted children and did
unspeakable things to them
saw me as beneath them.
Forty years.
Forty long, hard years.
Honor.
It was true honor, I tell you.
Forty years ago, I was at the
top of the world, a shining star.
And my former glory will return, I swear.
My wisdom on feng shui,
which rendered me the only survivor of
that fire, appeared in the form of a stand.
As sure as I'm floating
here glaring at you,
people will soon call me Founder once
again, and they will all follow me?
even if I never see
outside this prison again.
The only thing I have left
to do now is finish you off.
For the last time, you show me.
I command you now, Drake Dream.
You will show me the precise
direction of my finishing attack.
Over there, FF!
On the other side of the stairs!
There's a fire hose!
Run and grab it, hurry!
Hey, asshole!
Instead of just standing there
watching and giving commentary,
you could help out FF!
You're a stand user, right?
The two of you could beat
that old bastard together!
I'll help if FF dies.
Before I came here, helping
FF was never part of the deal.
The sworn agreement was
to protect only you.
And besides, FF said themself
not to step in for them.
They saw that you were injured when
we got here and asked me to protect
you from other dangerous enemies who
are still in the punishment cells.
Where is it?
I've got to get the water running now!
Where the hell is the faucet?
Be careful what you touch.
This is your unlucky direction.
You must protect it fiercely.
Otherwise, a definite
attack will head your way.
There's no time to be doing
something silly like drinking water.
At their own will!
FF, no! What are you doing? Please stop!
An attack has already
been decided, get it?
This is not going to end well for you!
Okay.
Rather than a decided attack
or being led into bad luck,
it looks like more than anything else,?
what FF really needs is water.
They purposely removed their arms
to fit their body into the hose.
Oh, they did it!
They managed to get...
This is your arm.
Feng Shui assassination has now begun. Ah,
it's obvious you wanted to get
some water and clearly you need it,
but I'm delighted to inform you that
nothing will go your way anymore.
My attacks will continue to become
your bad fortune from here on out.
That's Feng Shui
assassination, Drake's dream.
It's all predetermined.
You cannot stop destiny.
They almost got water, but then couldn't.
He wouldn't even let them touch it.
What's going to happen now?
Directly beneath the discipline
cell here is the execution room.
Remember, it's Florida.
Capital punishment is a big thing here.
Two or three people every
year are executed by
electrocution in the chair
down in the basement.
And it uses 2,800 volts.
This sucks.
I can't believe I missed it.
I was so close to the water.
But I was able to break the faucet off.
I'll just have to get the
water from up there now.
If things don't change.
The planktons would certainly be
annihilated in less than a second.
Holy shit!
Is this the chair?
What the hell?
It's coming down.
Is it already live?
What is that many turns on
when the counter hits zero?
Fuck that!
If I can help it, it won't!
I was curious.
After I unleash my attacks, what's
the end going to look like for you?
That situation anyone could perfectly
predict what was going to happen?
He could kiss my ass look at the
water dripping from above before that!
It looks like it's already been decided.
You're supposed to be
sitting in that chair.
Don't fight it.
You'll never get your water, so give up.
And the timing's absolutely perfect.
The precise time of the finishing blow.
Oh god, FF!
Yes, the definitive direction of attack,
and the perfect direction of protection.
Feng Shui assassination.
It took 40 years to achieve, but this
can only mean that I finally mastered it.
The founder has been resurrected at last!
With this, I'll go down
in history as a Buddha,
equivalent in power and
glory to Shaka Mooney!
Yee-hah-hah-hah!
I'm neutral, old man, so it's not like
I'm gonna help you out or anything.
But you see, FF did
manage to obtain water.
Mere moments ago, in fact,
when you kicked them.
Wanna know how?
Because a 78-year-old like
you ran around hysterically,
You perspired abundantly
because FF made you run around.
Your sweat is the water they
used, and you missed it.
It appears that FF can
create mirrors using sweat.
All it takes is about a third of
a glass to make a functional one.
You provided more than enough for them.
In other words, if you're
looking at a reflection of me,
that's not at all your safe direction.
In fact, quite the opposite.
It's an official tie.
The only thing that'll seal away the
perfect feng shui assassination is a tie!
FF made their resolve
specifically for this!
Take this and choke on it!
If I can share some good fortune with you!
What did I say? The legend!
Yeah, Brian!
Well, it's over.
What's going to happen next?
You'll keep looking for the bone, right?
That's really what you
should be focused on now.
Silver lining.
At least there's no way Kenzo's feng shui
assassination can attack you anymore?
Despite the sacrifice for it we know
it was indeed an invincible stand!
Preposterous!
Hey Jolyn Kujo!
What do you think you're doing?
The damage your body has suffered is far
more severe and extensive than you realize!
Also you should know by now
that the planktons inside FF
were already killed by the
2800 volts shot through them!
You couldn't possibly repair that!
The dragon!
The dragon is still there!
So did they let go of
Kenzo's hand too early?
I guess this happened because planktons
can't handle electricity like humans can!
Kenzo!
How is he still alive?
What are you doing?
Are you trying to release
your stand in your condition?
Is the raw fury of revenge driving this?
We're not leaving him like this.
Let's end it right now.
Don't own it!
Nice try, but you'll never hit me.
I'm going to annihilate you and then
I'll be back as the founder at last!
I see, so that's how it is.
Now it's patently clear.
That's his safe direction.
I understand.
You were trying to figure out
the place Kenzo just escaped to.
If you can track down the actual safe
spot that's protected from all attacks,
then the FFs that scattered,
along with the sweat that they
used to create the mirror,
should still be safe and intact there.
It should have been safe even
from the 2800 volt surge.
You attacked the old man
to find that exact spot.
F-Faps survived!
I fucking knew it!
Holy shit, that's amazing!
Hey, Jolene!
Do you truly think you've beaten me?
You believe you could force me to
surrender with that pathetic attempt?
I'm going to finish you off, Jolene Kujo.
My plan to do so has never wavered.
You will never get away.
Do you refuse to see?
You're already lying in the dead center of
the direction of my
Feng Shui assassination.
There's no escape, so you
might as well give up.
Stone Ocean's threat is finding
its way inside the dragon.
My attack is imminent, woman.
Your bad fortune is an absolute reality.
No matter what attack
I choose to use on you,
your demise has been chosen
and you cannot evade it.
Yes, I won
Bow down before me.
There's no change in
reviving the founder either
Hey!
I hit her, didn't I, Drake's dream?
All you have to do is confirm it.
My instant death kick.
It hit Jolene, which means my Feng Shui
assassination is definite and true.
Speak, you silly lizard.
Am I right?
Yeah, your finishing blow
definitely smashed right into her.
Then why is Jolene safe and
sound down there and I'm
barely clinging onto this
railing like a broken spider?
Huh?
Dragon, tell me the
safe direction now! Huh?
Hey, waste dragon, come back!
Why are you drifting away?
Tell me my safe direction
and hurry up! But why?
Why are you coming with me?
I'm the one who wants to
say those words, old man.
You're the one drifting away.
You're the one who let go voluntarily
and started falling to the ground.
You have no one to blame
but yourself, you fool!
What are you doing to me?
I told you, give your direction to me.
And I told you, you're the one
drifting away from me, old man.
I can't help you.
By the way, about your legs,
they look very strange.
There must be something
terribly wrong with them.
When you were kicking Jolene before, did
they perhaps do something to your legs?
What the?
What is that?
I know what Jolene's threat stand
looks like, and that's not it.
Could it possibly be?
The stand that's emerging
from inside Jolene is...
Dive or drive, and I insured
it dove into her body itself.
See, if a particular attack
on Jolene has been decided,
then that just means I protect her right
when the kick lands, no matter what.
What the hell is happening?
My name!
This man that FF brought
with them, Anastasia.
He slipped his own powerful
stand into my body,
and then it permanently destroyed
both of Kenzo's legs like that.
He basically turned his flesh and
bones into a giant pile of plasma.
Then just as quickly, he reassembled
them into functional springs.
A suspension of flesh and bone!
Kenzo doesn't feel pain right now.
That goes for me, too,
because of the stand that made the
prisoners and guards fight each other.
Although...
Ahhhh!
She spared nothing, even my hips!
Give me my safe direction, dragon!
I can't reach!
Don't go that way!
This guy is an ally?
A guy who would do something so brutal.
I mean, who is he, really?
That's it.
Yes, this is perfect.
You just keep looking at
me with those pretty eyes.
Don't take your eyes off of me.
Your safe direction is northeast,
and your lucky color, cerulean blue.
But I must inform you,
you're all out of chances.
In only a few minutes of battle,
you've aged exponentially further.
Although you think I cope,
my head is filled with hope.
Of some place
other than here!
Although you think I smile,
Inside and all the while,
I'm wondering?
About my destiny!
I'm thinking about,
All the things I'd
like to do in my life!
I'm a dreamer,
a distant dreamer!
Dreaming for all!
From today.
Jolene! Are you okay?
Yeah.
I just started to feel
a lot of pain suddenly.
But we need to find them now.
You know the bone?
And the little guy that picked it up?
Just wait a few minutes.
I'm gonna repair your wounds now.
Yeah, but hurry.
We have to get it back, and fast.
It has Tad's disc.
you Thank you.